

- in
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/sa dor-akhmatov-45a627291/
- +998 948201777
- $\vee$
- sardor.akhmatov0969@gmail.com
- 0
- Tashkent, Uzbekistan



https://github.com/AkhmatovSardor

## HARD SKILLS

- Java(OOP, Collection), Postgresql
- Swagger, Redis
- Spring (Boot, Framework, Data, Security)
- Git (Github, Gitlab), Docker (Docker Hub)
- Package Manager (Maven, Gradle)
- Microservice architecture Configuration
- Cloud configuration, Service Registry,
- Load Balancing, Eureka, Gateway
- Breaker (Circuit breaker, Rate-Limiter
- Time-limiter, Cache).

#### SOFT SKILLS

- OOP,Data Structure
- Clean code
- JUnit test
- Linux
- Telegram bot
- JPA-Hibernate
- Deploymant

## EDUCATION

SECONDARY SCHOOL

TATU 2022-present

lsystem It Academy 2022-2023

# AKHMATOV SARDOR

ABOUT ME

I am a Java backend developer. I love new technologies, innovations and new challenges in IT. Learning new things is my favorite job. I'm into problem solving, which is what I do every day to solve some problem while working, and I'm a math lover. After I get a deep knowledge of Java, I create a team to carry out projects. Now my team and I are developing several start-up projects. I have strong communication skills combined with experience.

Date of birth: 15.11.2004

Place of birth: Samarkand

Nationality: Uzbek

# EXPERIENCE

JAVA DEVELOPER

2022-present

O

⋖

Worked as a mentor (assistant) at Isystem It Academy for 6 months in the field of Java backend.

Nowadays, I am getting offer from some companies to write their back-end, also i finished one back-end project of marketplace that will be available soon

#### ADDITIONAL EDUCATION

### ISYSTEM IT ACADEMY

2022-2023

Completed Java Backend course at [Isystem It Academy]. Received a certificate for completing an offline course.

# FREELANCE

To create a start-up project, which is a CRM platform that brings together the manufacturer, sellers and customers It is the automation of various business processes in the villages, and my responsibility is to build the architecture, develop

business logic with microservice architecture and securely data transfer to receive client requests in response • project testing, to automate the deployment of the project on the server